Kazami, get away from him!
Kazami, menyingkir!
So it was you...
Sudah kuduga ternyata kau.
(Original: Gosho Aoyama)
(Karya asli, Gosho Aoyama)
An unidentified bomber.
Pelaku ledakan masih belum jelas,
He's based in Russia
namun ia berasal dari Rusia,
and people call him Pramya and fear him.
ditakuti sebagai Pramya.
(Director: Susumu Mitsunaka)
(Sutradara, Susumu Mitsunaka)
(Script: Takahiro Ohkura) and people call him Pramya and fear him.
(Skenario, Okura Takahiro) ditakuti sebagai Pramya.
This was a trap to lure Amuro-san out.
Ternyata ini jebakan untuk memancing Amuro!
(Music: Yugo Kanno)
(Musik, Yugo Kanno)
(Criminal Department, Sergeant Jinpei Matsuda) I still remember most of the week I spent with that guy.
(Sersan Jinpei Matsuda) Aku masih ingat sepekanku dengannya.
(Now, "the past" is surfacing) I still remember most of the week I spent with that guy.
(Masa Lalu yang Akan Terungkap)
(Now, "the past" is surfacing) Please don't tell Takagi-kun.
Jangan bilang Takagi, ya.
(Metropolitan Police Academy) Four of your peers have passed away, right?
(Sekolah Kepolisian Metropolitan) 4 orang dari teman sekelasmu itu sudah meninggal, kan?
(The "time" starts to tick) Don't interfere with me!
(Waktu Mulai Bergerak) Jangan mengangguku!
You came. I've been waiting underneath.
Kutunggu di bawah.
They've risked their lives...
Ia mempertaruhkan nyawa.
I can't let that be squandered.
Tak bisa kusia-siakan!
(Theme Song "Chronostasis" by BUMP OF CHICKEN (Toy's Factory))
(Lagu Tema "Chronotasis" BUMP OF CHICKEN, Toy's Factory)
The scramble of fate that's lit by fire.
Takdir yang apinya telah dinyalakan.
And the fated opponent who appeared in Tokyo again.
Kemudian, lawan yang ditakdirkan muncul lagi Tokyo.
If a detective gives up his case and quits, that'd be his defeat.
Bila detektif membiarkan suatu kasus,
(Name: Jinpei Matsuda) If a detective gives up his case and quits,
kemudian berhenti, berarti dia kalah, kan?
(Bomb Set Off On Sky Wheel In Haido Town Officer Died When Defusing) that'd be his defeat.
(Ledakan di Bianglala Raksasa Pusat Perbelanjaan Kota Haido) kemudian berhenti, berarti dia kalah, kan?
The one who I've been loving and yearning for is...
Orang yang kusuka,
Now, this festal Halloween
Sekarang, perayaan halloween ini,
is becoming the highway to madness.
akan berubah jadi kereta malam yang gila!
No way!
Tidak mungkin!
(As long as I'm alive...)
( Selama masih hidup- )
I'll never let you die.
Takkan kubiarkan kau mati.
(The will is inherited)
(Perasaan Juga Akan Terus Diwariskan)
This time, I won't let you get away.
Takkan kubiarkan kau kabur lagi.
I won't let you have your own way anymore.
Takkan kubiarkan kau berbuat seenaknya!
Detective Conan the movie: The Bride of Halloween.
Layar Lebar Detective Conan,
I'll leave the rest to you.
Kuserahkan sisanya padamu.
Don't tell me you're gonna...
Jangan-jangan...
Amuro-san!
Amuro!